<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[42]]></id><name><![CDATA[leguide]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LeGuide.com]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Comparatori di prezzo]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[   LeGuide]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-comparatori-prezzo/42-leguidecom.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/42.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[   LeGuide.com Group, il network di guide commerciali, siti di confronto dei prezzi, i motori di ricerca dello shopping e forum on-line dei consumatori, è il leader di dominio in Francia e numero 2 in Europa, con 12.800.000 visitatori unici. La società è un intermediario di fiducia tra utenti e siti di negozio, e aiuta i clienti con ogni fase della loro acquisti online, aiutandoli a colpire così in alto acquisti attraverso decine e decine di offerte speciali. LeGuide.com Group è presente in 14 paesi ed elenca più di 60.000 negozi on-line e 135 milioni di prodotti. (* Comscore aprile 2010)   Leguide.com Features   Va vous permettre Le modulo d'sincronizzatore e l'ensemble de votre boutique en vers LeGuide.com automatiquement PRENANT en compte à l'ordonnancement spécifique LeGuide.com Cela va vous donner de la possibilité Développer activité et votre de mettre en avant votre site et vos Meilleures offres.    Retrouvez l'ensemble des moduli de comparateurs de prix pour PrestaShop dans la catégorie comparateurs de prix PrestaShop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module gives you the opportunity to develop your business and highlight your site your best deals!  When you sell products online, it&rsquo;s essential that potential customers can find their way to your site. Whether they are trying to unearth a particular product or are simply trying to find the cheapest offer, buyers are using shopping guides more and more; having a listing on a price comparison website is therefore vital if you want to make yourself known to millions of buyers about to make a purchase and thus boost your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.17]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595088-pprod/leguidecom.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595088-pbig/leguidecom.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[367]]></id><name><![CDATA[banipmod]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Ban IP addresses]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Strumenti per l’amministrazione]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Banna gli utenti indesiderati dal tuo negozio]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-amministrazione/367-ban-ip-addresses.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/367.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Banna gli utenti indesiderati dal tuo negozio]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Proteggi il tuo sito dagli utenti malintenzionati e dai robot indesiderati]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/613667-pprod/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/613667-pbig/ban-ip-addresses.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5 - Create ​​bundles of products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandizing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/merchandizing-prestashop-modulo/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows the sale batch using any stocks actually available products composing your packs, and offers the opportunity to apply business operations.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Allow the purchase of combinations of products with or without a discount, in one click  Would you like to increase your average shopping cart and at the same time, allow your customers to save money if they purchase several products simultaneously? It is now possible thanks to&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;!  Without waiting any longer, you can create packs of products that can be purchased in one click, without worrying about stock or their combinations.  A precious additional sales tool  Accompany your customers in their buying process, by offering them&nbsp;packs of coherent products&nbsp;that you will have predefined, just as the salesman in a real shop would do. Such as for example: this fantastic camera, memory card and tripod. You know that this selection is appropriate and that it will appeal to your customers.  Or you could even use your best-sellers, by adding them to those that are less visible, to allow your customers to discover them.  Your packs will need to be made up of 2 products minimum, the number is unlimited. Push the quantity per product, choose the combinations of your choice, there are multiple options allowing you to multiply the possibilities.  Would you like to reserve the purchase of a product within a pack? That is also possible! You will therefore be able&nbsp;to offer a free product&nbsp;if it is purchased as part of a pack. The possibilities are infinite!  Integrated assistant  It isn&#39;t always obvious deciding which products should be offered within a pack. Here again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution to the problem. When creating your pack, our module will supply you with strategic information, like the number of products sold or their available stock. There is also an integrated&nbsp;dynamic price simulator&nbsp;for your pack, to help you see more clearly when creating your business transaction, without you harming your profit margin.  Remain the maestro of combinations  One of the products that you have added to your pack is available in several colors, but you don&#39;t want to offer them all in this set? Advanced Pack&nbsp;will allow you to do this.  You will also have the possibility of predefining a combination by default, for each of the products of your pack, even if it&#39;s different to the one defined in your catalog.  Your customers will then be able to&nbsp;personalise their selection&nbsp;amongst the characteristics that you will have chosen to integrate in the offer.  Business Incentive  Incentive is something that motivates your visitor to make a purchase The main aim is to convince more of your site visitors to finish their order and/or&nbsp;spend more money per transaction. Perhaps you have already tried, by offering free delivery over a certain amount of purchases, or to offer discounts on certain products or even to send discount vouchers? All of these methods work, but their range is limited, as these promotions are usually temporary due to their excessive cost! Stop looking, you have already found the solution !  To entice your customers,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will give you the choice of applying a discount when all the products in the shopping cart are ordered, thus encouraging the purchase of the whole pack.  3 possibilities are available:&nbsp;Offer a specific discount on&nbsp;each product&nbsp;in the packApply a general discount on&nbsp;the set of productsApply a&nbsp;fixed price, such as a psychological price, for example Advanced Pack&nbsp;will also be able to manage the discounts already applied to your products, allowing you to integrate them in the pack price, or on the contrary, to exclude them, in order to choose the predefined discount on the pack. This decision will be made even easier thanks to our&nbsp;clear and clean-looking interface, that will allow you to see the discounted products very easily.  You won&#39;t need to worry about the coherence of your prices anymore  Have you ever had to review all the prices in your catalog, to detect any possible incoherences and correct them? What would happen if you had to manually manage the repercussions of these changes in product pricing in your packs? This would represent a significant extra workload if if it&#39;s not anticipated within the choice of management solutions within your packs!  Once again&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;has the solution.  By default, in the case where no reduction has been applied, the pack price is the sum of the products making it up. Should you need to modify the price of a product after having created the pack,&nbsp;the pack price will automatically be updated, and without you having to intervene.  In those cases where you will apply a discount to one or more products in an existing pack, and on condition you have authorized the&nbsp;promotional implications, the pack price will also be changed, showing your customers the discount that has been applied.  Is one of the products of your pack subject to an green-tax? No problem, it will automatically be reflected in the pack price and will be clearly stated, guaranteeing absolute&nbsp;respect for the legislation.  Regarding the management of your stock, everything has been automated!  For each pack ordered, the product stocks it contains will be&nbsp;automatically deducted. This way you will avoid the double management of stock or the frustration generated by sales rendered impossible, due to the bad assignation of quantities. Also, in the case where a product in a pack is out of stock, it will&nbsp;automatically be displayed as unavailable&nbsp;for purchase thanks to an availability warning system that is both elegant and modern.  For your customers, we have integrated a graphic and fun notification system, allowing the instant identification of stock shortages on combinations or products making up the pack.&nbsp;There&#39;s no chance of you receiving orders for products that are out of stock !  Highlight your packs and sell more  Once you have defined your pack, you will be able to configure it in the same way as you would a classic product. Everything is possible, such as assigning it customized images, classing it in the category of your choice,&nbsp;optimizing your SEO, writing a customized description, attributing it an EAN code or a specific reference, configuring its volume to calculate delivery costs, etc...  For those that are pressed for time, and in order to facilitate their marketing,&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;will automatically display all the photos of the products that make it up, as well as their descriptions, in the form of tabs. Your customers will be correctly informed, without leaving the page of your pack, and&nbsp;able to finalise their purchase in one click.  And that&#39;s not all... For more visibility, your packs will automatically be&nbsp;highlighted on their data sheets&nbsp;for those being sold in lots This way, you will encourage your customers to order the pack, rather than the product they were initially interested in. Essentially, this is&nbsp;cross-selling: an accessible method of&nbsp;increasing your average shopping cart&nbsp;!  We don&#39;t forget designers  From the beginning, we have integrated the fact that this module should be easily adapted by your web agency or designer/integrator. The module adapts itself perfectly to the default PrestaShop 1.5 and 1.6 themes, whilst allowing the most advanced graphic personalization.  A set of JavaScript templates and CSS style sheets are delivered as models with the module,&nbsp;to facilitate the integration process. Either yourself or your integrator will therefore be able to use all of the functionalities of the&nbsp;Advanced Pack 5&nbsp;engine, in order to present them in the graphic form that will best correspond with the general atmosphere of your online store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[269.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1504]]></id><name><![CDATA[upstrackingv2]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[UPS Delivery Status]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Trasporto & Logistica]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Proponi ai tuoi clienti la consegna con UPS, operatore chiave dell'e-commerce, e accedi al tracking delle tue spedizioni direttamente dal tuo Back-office PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/trasporto-logistica-moduli-prestashop/1504-ups-delivery-status.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1504.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Proponi ai tuoi clienti la consegna con UPS, operatore chiave dell'e-commerce, e accedi al tracking delle tue spedizioni direttamente dal tuo Back-office PrestaShop.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Migliora la rassicurazione del tuo sito proponendo UPS, il n°1 nella distribuzione di pacchi negli Stati Uniti.Ottimizza le tue conversioni proponendo ai tuoi clienti una consegna rapida e tracciata.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/611439-pprod/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611439-pbig/ups-delivery-status.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1615]]></id><name><![CDATA[gshopping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Shopping]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Comparatori di prezzo]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Esporta facilmente il tuo catalogo verso Google Shopping, il nuovo comparatore di prezzo sviluppato da Google! Attenzione: Questo modulo necessita di sottoscrivere a un servizio terzo]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-comparatori-prezzo/1615-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/1615.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Esporta facilmente il tuo catalogo verso Google Shopping, il nuovo comparatore di prezzo sviluppato da Google! Attenzione: Questo modulo necessita di sottoscrivere a un servizio terzo. Ti preghiamo di sottoscrivere il servizio di Google prima di ordinare questo modulo.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Gli annunci con scheda di prodotto vengono pubblicati quando un utente cerca i tuoi prodotti su google.it e google.com/shopping. Con gli annunci con scheda di prodotto paghi solo quando un utente fa clic sul tuo annuncio e viene reindirizzato sul tuo sito web. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595182-pprod/google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595182-pbig/google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces e reselling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Esclusiva di Prestashop Addons, il modulo Amazon Market Place è la soluzione n° 1 per mettere online i propri prodotti su Amazon e gestire gli ordini del marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/marketplace-affiliation-prestashop-moduli/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Esclusiva di Prestashop Addons, il modulo Amazon Market Place è la soluzione n° 1 per mettere online i propri prodotti su Amazon e gestire gli ordini del marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Puoi integrare in modo semplice il tuo negozio Prestashop al primo marketplace mondiale e aumentare significativamente le vendite. Puoi importare gli ordini nel tuo negozio Prestashop e centralizzare le scorte.  Gestire in modo efficace il tuo negozio e onorare rapidamente gli ordini Amazon permette di aumentare il grado di soddisfazione dei clienti e quindi automaticamente anche il tuo indice di prestazioni venditore.  L'ideazione del modulo si basa sull'esperienza iniziale di commercianti elettronici; il modulo è stato elaborato da un commerciante elettronico al servizio dei suoi colleghi e sviluppato da un'équipe di sviluppatori professionisti, cosa che gli conferisce semplicità di utilizzo e massima efficacia.  Il tuo acquisto è garantito da supporto tecnica gratuita, assicurata incondizionatamente fino alla messa in rete dei prodotti e l'importo dei tuoi primi ordini.  Questo modulo è stato sviluppato da Common-Services, agenzia partner di Prestashop, presente su Prestashop Addons dal 2010 e produttrice di altri 15 moduli best seller, commercializzati unicamente su Prestashop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.040]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Ricerca & Filtri]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Vincitore del Best Module Award Proponete il motore di ricerca avanzata più veloce sul mercato]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/ricerca-filtri-prestashop-moduli/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Vincitore del Best Module Award Proponete il motore di ricerca avanzata più veloce sul mercato]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Proponete ai vostri clienti una selezione di prodotti corrispondenti alle loro attese.  Strumento indispensabile per i negozi che offrono una vasta selezione di prodotti, Advanced Search 4 permette di aggiungere tutti i motori di ricerca che desiderate e di sistemarli in diverse posizioni sul vostro sito.  Questo modulo è stato sviluppato con l'obiettivo di fornire tempi di caricamento ridotti, anche per grossi cataloghi.  I vostri visitatori potranno scorrere i prodotti secondo i loro criteri di ricerca per effettuare i loro acquisti in breve tempo.  Vincitore dei Best Modules Awards 2012  Advanced Search 4 è stato eletto miglior modulo dellʾanno durante il BarCamp PrestaShop di Barcellona (Spagna) !  Strumento indispensabile per i negozi che offrono una vasta selezione di prodotti.  Advanced Search 4 aggiunge la multi navigazione sfaccettata, la ricerca per tappe, filtri e ricerca multi criterio. Ogni ricerca è memorizzata durante la navigazione dei vostri clienti e permette loro di ritrovare i risultati delle loro ricerche in qualsiasi momento.  Google è suo amico  Questo modulo PrestaShop permette una piccola rivoluzione per le vostre referenze. Potrete generare delle pagine prodotto in grande quantità, ottimizzate per il SEO e senza duplicazione di contenuti grazie ad Advanced Search 4! Selezionate i criteri per i quali volete migliorare le vostre referenze, convalidate ed eccovi con centinaia di pagine con le liste dei prodotti con : URL riscritto, tag H1, descrizioni, tag, link incrociati automatici…  Per massimizzare la vostra notorietà, le pagine di risultati potranno essere condivise sui principali social network, ma anche per e-mail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.10.14]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573189-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Modifica rapida / di massa]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!You have over than 100 products?  You want to control the association of your products to your categories?  This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/modifica-rapida-prestashop-moduli/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products!You have over than 100 products?  You want to control the association of your products to your categories?  This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time!In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category.Look for products that you want to add this category and add 1 click!You also control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/51759-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/51759-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[storemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[STORE MANAGER]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Strumenti per l’amministrazione]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily]]></description><author><![CDATA[eMagicOne]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-amministrazione/2937-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-DAY FREE TRIAL!&nbsp;&nbsp;The back office solution you need to run your PrestaShop online store efficiently ! Store Manager for PrestaShop&nbsp;will save you over 2 hours a day by automating daily tasks&nbsp;and making it simple to update your shop. &nbsp; Store Manager for PrestaShop is a desktop application, designed to speed up and automate the management of PrestaShop based stores. Not only does it take care of the mass operations with products, categories, orders and customers extending the functionality of the store web back-end, but also lines up with an intuitive interface and advanced addons for easy store management. Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; *** WINNER OF THE PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE *** &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save your time, money, and resources by allowing Store Manager for PrestaShop do all the job for you. Store Manager for PrestaShop will make your store stand out from the crowd! &nbsp; Spend an Hour, Save a Day! Store Manager for PrestaShop was designed to work for you and not at the expense of your business. It is your personal assistant that does all the routine tasks, saving you tons of time for greater deeds. For that matter, it provides with ready-made export/import features, report tools, advanced addons, etc. No need to spend a day getting deep into how your store works, spend an hour understanding how Store Manager does the job for you. &nbsp; Take Your Online Business to the Bank Buy one Store Manager instead of multiple modules. Use one Store Manager license to manage your multiple stores. Store Manager doesn&rsquo;t require any special skills, so you don&rsquo;t have to pay someone to keep your store database organized. You can implement all the necessary updates yourself with Store Manager for PrestaShop and get on to important tasks. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[]]></version><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/689783-pprod/store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/689783-pbig/store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3162]]></id><name><![CDATA[webcallback]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Call Back]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Chiudere più vendite con l'aggiunta del modulo di chiamata Torna al tuo negozio online!  Il pulsante di richiamo fornisce ai vostri clienti un utile apprezzato anche da: essere chiamato gratuitamente ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/3162-call-back.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3162.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Chiudere più vendite con l'aggiunta del modulo di chiamata Torna al tuo negozio online!  Il pulsante di richiamo fornisce ai vostri clienti un utile apprezzato anche da: essere chiamato gratuitamente per ricevere, faccia a faccia ulteriori informazioni su un prodotto, controllo di processo, sicurezza dei pagamenti ...]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Rassicura i tuoi clienti per telefono spiegando loro in prima persona tutti gli attributi e i vantaggi dei tuoi prodotti e concludi così più vendite!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611422-pprod/call-back.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611422-pbig/call-back.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3252]]></id><name><![CDATA[printlabels]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Stampa di etichette Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Strumenti per l’amministrazione]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Risparmia tempo prezioso automatizzando la modifica delle tue etichette di consegna! Modifica e stampa le tue etichette di consegna e incollale direttamente sui pacchi degli ordini da spedire]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-amministrazione/3252-print-labels.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3252.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Risparmia tempo prezioso automatizzando la modifica delle tue etichette di consegna! Modifica e stampa le tue etichette di consegna e incollale direttamente sui pacchi degli ordini da spedire.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Risparmia tempo nella spedizione dei tuoi ordiniRiduci i tuoi tassi di reso dei prodotti dovuto a indirizzi errati]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595260-pprod/print-labels.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595260-pbig/print-labels.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3438]]></id><name><![CDATA[auctions]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Auctions]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/3438-auctions.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3438.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Auctions module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. With a number of great features and intuitive interface, this is the best auctions module available for Prestashop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module was created to give merchants ability to sell products on auctions in easiest possible way. Auctions are the great way to attract and keep customers in your shop. You will be sure that customer is paying right price for your products. You don't have to negotiate prices with customers anymore. Managing auctions is very intuitive, and fully integrated with your shop. You will feel like it's not a module but integral part of the PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/625145-pprod/auctions.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625145-pbig/auctions.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[3511]]></id><name><![CDATA[priceminister]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PriceMinister]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces e reselling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Traete vantaggio dalla notoriet&agrave; di PriceMinister con i suoi 2 milioni di visite al giorno e i suoi 20 milioni di iscritti e aumentate le vendite con il vostro negozio super-PriceMinister]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/marketplace-affiliation-prestashop-moduli/3511-priceminister.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/3511.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Traete vantaggio dalla notoriet&agrave; di PriceMinister con i suoi 2 milioni di visite al giorno e i suoi 20 milioni di iscritti e aumentate le vendite con il vostro negozio super-PriceMinister.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[&nbsp;Con il modulo PriceMinister Prestashop la gestione &egrave; automatizzata, i prodotti vengono esportati direttamente e importati automaticamente nel luogo dove avviene la vendita di PriceMinister, e i vostri ordini vengono automaticamente inseriti e integrati nel vostro negozio PrestaShop.&nbsp;  Inoltre renderete automatica anche la comunicazione con i vostri clienti: gli ordini successivi saranno inviati direttamente al cliente via e-mail, tramite il servizio web PriceMinister, i clienti saranno avvisati e lo stato degli ordini automaticamente aggiornato.&nbsp;  Utilizzando il modulo PriceMinister Prestashop conserverete anche il controllo dei vostri flussi di offerte e prodotti, potrete importare automaticamente i vostri ordini senza costi o sottoscrizioni aggiuntive, gli scambi di dati sono automatizzati e gratuiti.&nbsp;  L&#39;integrazione &egrave; facile e conveniente, dopo aver configurato il modulo, il vostro export diventa automatico, in modo da non dover pi&ugrave; mettere mano sui dati.&nbsp;  L&#39;installazione di operazioni pianificate &egrave; semplice e automatizzata grazie alla compatibilit&agrave; con il modulo Prestashop Editor (gratuito).&nbsp;  Basta fare clic su un pulsante per integrare automaticamente le operazioni previste dal modulo, che possono comunque essere configurate manualmente. Il disegno del modulo si basa su un&rsquo;esperienza di e-shopping, il modulo &egrave; stato sviluppato da un esperto di vendite online al servizio dei suoi colleghi e sviluppato da sviluppatori professionisti, che gli conferisce facilit&agrave; d&#39;uso e massima efficienza.&nbsp;  Il vostro acquisto &egrave; protetto da un supporto tecnico gratuito e assicurato incondizionatamente fino alla messa in rete dei prodotti e l&#39;importazione dei vostri primi ordini.&nbsp;   Avete bisogno di un account PRO PriceMinister.&nbsp;Mercato : Francese.  Nuova versione, v4 PriceMinister: esportazione XML, configurazione semplificata, le operazioni previste originali, mappatura intelligente, design elegante, una migliore ergonomia.  Questo modulo &egrave; stato sviluppato da Common-Services, agenzia partner di Prestashop, presente su Prestashop Addons dal 2010 e produttrice di altri 15 moduli best seller, commercializzati unicamente su Prestashop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.09]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[179.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[244.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[144.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654537-pprod/priceminister.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/654537-pbig/priceminister.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation FB]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pubblicità & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/pubblicita-marketing-newsletter-moduli/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !  This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[164.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Loyalty"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-2015-loyalty.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation-fb.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4549]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmurealtimestats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Real Time Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Statistiche & Analisi]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/analytics-prestashop-moduli/4549-dmu-real-time-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4549.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Visualize in Real Time every visitor on your shop !With this module you are no longer blind! you are able to know everything about the activity of your shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module lets you know exactly what is happening on your shop.Now you are able to visualize the path of a visitor, his reactions on each page visited, ease or blocking steps in the ordering process ... ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.9]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[84.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pprod/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/324796-pbig/dmu-real-time-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4932]]></id><name><![CDATA[mynewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[My Newsletter & Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pubblicità & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Fidelizzare i clienti inviando loro una newsletter aziendale, e ottimizzare sempre dalle statistiche di monitoraggio! Il tuo negozio invia la newsletter senza avete bisogno di un router]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/pubblicita-marketing-newsletter-moduli/4932-my-newsletter-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4932.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Fidelizzare i clienti inviando loro una newsletter aziendale, e ottimizzare sempre dalle statistiche di monitoraggio! Il tuo negozio invia la newsletter senza avete bisogno di un router.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[La tua newsletter personalizzata inviata pochi click!  Fidelizzare i clienti ed informarli delle vostre promozioni e le notizie in modo molto semplice con questo modulo per PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.24]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[139.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595046-pprod/my-newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595046-pbig/my-newsletter-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Indicizzazione – SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Migliora la tua SEO grazie all'Internal Linking]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/seo-moduli-prestashop/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Migliora la tua SEO grazie all'Internal Linking]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Ottimizza la SEO del tuo negozio PrestaShop  L'Internal Linking consiste nella creazione di collegamenti tra le pagine del tuo negozio, utilizzando parole chiave per le quali vuoi raggiungere un migliore posizionamento su Google.  Per ottimizzare al meglio la SEO del tuo sito Internet, è fondamentale realizzare un Internal Linking che permetterà ai motori di ricerca di esplorare il tuo negozio nel modo più semplice possibile. L'obiettivo è quello di fornire loro il massimo delle informazioni con il minimo di clic possibile.  L'Internal Linking SEO ottimizza per te l'organizzazione della navigazione all'interno del tuo negozio e gioca un ruolo essenziale nella tua strategia SEO.  Indica le espressioni per le quali vuoi essere indicizzato, insieme alle loro pagine di destinazione, e lascia che il modulo crei i collegamenti giusti per te!  Se desideri aggiungere dei collegamenti automatici alle tue descrizioni delle pagine, decidi di installare il nostro modulo HTML on Descriptions.  È veramente utile avere una buona struttura di collegamento interno?  Il collegamento di link interni con parole chiave precise costituisce un metodo di ottimizzazione dalla validità ormai comprovata. Soprattutto per rinforzare la rilevanza di un contenuto.  Tra gli inconvenienti, bisogna sapere che la creazione di questi collegamenti è lunga e fastidiosa, necessita di seguire delle regole di buona condotta SEO, al fine di non fare una sovra-ottimizzazione che possa essere rilevata da Google, e deve essere aggiornata regolarmente per andare di pari passo con le modifiche del tuo catalogo.  È in quest'ottica che abbiamo sviluppato questo modulo, che ti permetterà di ottenere in pochi minuti centinaia di collegamenti incrociati tra le tue pagine, con la sicurezza di rispettare le linee guida per le migliori pratiche di SEO White Hat.  Il nostro modulo è stato pensato per servire allo stesso modo sia le agenzie SEO che i commercianti online.  Il suo utilizzo è dei più semplici.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.1.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[124.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Rapporti avanzati di vendita, tassa, profitti e margine]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Statistiche & Analisi]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Producete dei rapporti professionali di vendita, IVA, profitti e margini in formato HTML o in CSV / Excel]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/analytics-prestashop-moduli/5255-rapporti-avanzati-di-vendita-tassa-profitti-e-margine.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Producete dei rapporti professionali di vendita, IVA, profitti e margini in formato HTML o in CSV / Excel.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Ottenete una perfetta visibilità sulla redditività del vostro negozio e dei vostri prodotti!  Il PrestaShop standard non fornisce strumenti che vi permettano di ottenere in un clic tutti i dati contabili che contano: IVA incassata, fatturato al netto dell’IVA dopo riduzione e soprattutto, degli importi relativi ai profitti e ai margini realizzati.  Questo modulo non vi fornisce soltanto tutte queste misure, ma vi permette anche di rispondere a domande come "quali percentuali delle mie vendite e/o profitti totali sono rappresentate da una marca, un fornitore o una categoria di prodotto in particolare?".   Questo modulo dall’interfaccia in AJAX moderna e piacevole vi permette di generare diversi tipi di rapporto preformattati con tutti questi dati. Possono essere visualizzati sullo schermo in HTML per una semplice consultazione, o esportati in formato CSV per modifiche in Excel o importati in un altro sistema informativo o di contabilità.  Questo modulo è pubblicato da Business Tech, editore certificato da PrestaShop e vincitore dei PrestaShop Awards 2011 nella categoria Miglior Modulo.  Avrete la sicurezza di acquistare un modulo di qualità e di disporre di un servizio di supporto tecnico operativo e efficace.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.8.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.2.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[204.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Time Saver"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/awards-2015-savetime.png]]></badge><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/543344-pprod/rapporti-avanzati-di-vendita-tassa-profitti-e-margine.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/543344-pbig/rapporti-avanzati-di-vendita-tassa-profitti-e-margine.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5275]]></id><name><![CDATA[productsbycategoryslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Slider - Products of same category]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Slider]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Invia articoli della stessa classe nelle vostre pagine di prodotti con questo dispositivo di scorrimento nella parte inferiore della pagina, e migliorare la navigazione dei vostri clienti, con il vost]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/diaporama-prestashop-moduli/5275-slider-products-of-same-category.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5275.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Invia articoli della stessa classe nelle vostre pagine di prodotti con questo dispositivo di scorrimento nella parte inferiore della pagina, e migliorare la navigazione dei vostri clienti, con il vostro paniere medio!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Questo modulo consente di effettuare cross-selling di altri prodotti in ogni categoria, e aumentare il paniere medio shopping.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/625266-pprod/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/625266-pbig/slider-products-of-same-category.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5542]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Preparazione di ordine semplificata]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Strumenti per l’amministrazione]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Risparmia preziosi minuti ogni giorno ottimizzando la tua logistica]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-amministrazione/5542-easy-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/5542.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Risparmia preziosi minuti ogni giorno ottimizzando la tua logistica]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Risparmia tempoSemplifica la tua logistica]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/613679-pprod/easy-order-preparation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/613679-pbig/easy-order-preparation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces e reselling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Vendi i tuoi prodotti sul marketplace di Cdiscount: esportazione cataloghi, aggiornamento automatico di prezzi e scorte, recupero e gestione degli ordini]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/marketplace-affiliation-prestashop-moduli/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Vendi i tuoi prodotti sul marketplace di Cdiscount: esportazione cataloghi, aggiornamento automatico di prezzi e scorte, recupero e gestione degli ordini.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le Marché è uno dei leader dei marketplace francesi.  Incrementa le vendite! Approfitta del traffico generato da Cdiscount per vendere i tuoi prodotti e beneficiare dei tanti vantaggi che rendono Cdiscount tanto popolare, come: - il pagamento in 4 rate (interamente sostenuto da Cdiscount) - le tante modalità di consegna…  Cdiscount si occupa di tutto! Proponi i tuoi prodotti sul marketplace e gestisci gli ordini, Cdiscount pensa a tutto il resto: traffico, facilità e sicurezza di pagamento, marketing…  1 solo back-office! Grazie al modulo Cdiscount per Prestashop, non hai bisogno di gestire diversi back-office. In pochi clic, connetti il tuo sito Prestashop al tuo negozio Cdiscount e pubblica le tue offerte in modo semplice: - Le schede-prodotto saranno esportate direttamente verso il marketplace di Cdiscount, - I prezzi e le scorte sono aggiornati automaticamente, - I tuoi ordini sono direttamente importati e integrati nel tuo negozio Prestashop.  Configurazione pratica e facile! Configura il tuo modulo, la tua esportazione diventa automatica, e così non dovrai elaborare altri dati.  Un modulo sviluppato da un venditore online, per i venditori online! La concezione del modulo si basa sull’esperienza iniziale dei venditori online, è stato elaborato da un venditore online al servizio dei suoi colleghi e sviluppato da un team di sviluppatori professionisti; per questo è estremamente efficace e semplice da utilizzare.  Supporto tecnico gratuito! Il tuo acquisto è garantito da un supporto tecnico gratuito che è assicurato senza condizioni fino alla messa online dei prodotti e l’importazione dei primi ordini.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.9.116]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[194.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[119.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616700-pprod/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/616700-pbig/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Caratteristiche senza limiti]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Ricerca & Filtri]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Definisci i dettagli delle caratteristiche dei tuoi prodotti]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/ricerca-filtri-prestashop-moduli/6356-multiple-features-caratteristiche-senza-limiti.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Definisci i dettagli delle caratteristiche dei tuoi prodotti]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Aggiungi caratteristiche senza limiti!  Con Multiple Features, per uno stesso prodotto e una stessa caratteristica, hai la possibilità di assegnare tutti i valori che vuoi. Potrai così superare una limitazione di PrestaShop e sfruttarne appieno le potenzialità!  Se in precedenza utilizzaviAdvanced Search 4 (Vincitore del Premio PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), adesso potrai offrire ai tuoi visitatori una ricerca ancora più pertinente nel tuo catalogo.  Caso cliente:  Ocarat.com: "Alcuni gioielli possono avere una composizione diversa e una lega di diversi metalli. Il Back Office di PrestaShop offre la possibilità di associare una caratteristica ad un prodotto. Ora, voglio aggiungere nel mio negozio un anello in oro con diamanti e smeraldi. Oggi, la scheda delle caratteristiche non mi permette di farlo. Non posso assegnare più valori ad uno stesso oggetto. Devo quindi scegliere tra oro, diamanti o smeraldi. Multiple Features ha tolto questa limitazione!"]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-caratteristiche-senza-limiti.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-caratteristiche-senza-limiti.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6413]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_cachemanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cache Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Indicizzazione – SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Dimezzate il tempo di ricarica delle vostre pagine]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/seo-moduli-prestashop/6413-cache-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6413.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Dimezzate il tempo di ricarica delle vostre pagine]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Migliorate il vostro tasso di trasformazione e il vostro posizionamento  Le statistiche sono una formalità: la ragione principale che spinge un utente ad abbandonare una pagina web è il tempo di caricamento.  Yahoo! dichiara che sul loro sito Auto. L'aggiunta di 400mb/s al caricamento della pagina aumenta il tasso di abbandono dal 5 al 9%. (Fonte Performance Web)  D'altronde, la velocità di visualizzazione è una garanzia di qualità che influenza molto positivamente il posizionamento nei motori di ricerca.  Permetterete così ai vostri clienti di approfittare di una maggior comodità di navigazione sul vostro sito, diminuendo i tempi di ricarica delle pagine, e facendogli guadagnare del tempo!  Offerta limitata: prezzi più bassi e soddisfatto o rimborsato !  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573569-pprod/cache-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573569-pbig/cache-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6414]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgabonos]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Credit Notes / Memos of the Complete Invoice in PDF]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Fatturazione]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Generate credit notes of the full invoice you need to cancel (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Unlimited number of credit notes]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/fatturazione-contabilita-moduli-prestashop/6414-credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/6414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Generate credit notes of the full invoice you need to cancel (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Unlimited number of credit notes. Issue the notes in PDF format and send them to your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[TO READ BEFORE PURCHASING THE MODULE Our module is only able to issue full credit notes (not possible to generate partial credit notes). Each credit note generated by our module automatically cancels the whole order, it's not possible to generate partial credit notes for just some products of the order. If you need partial credit notes, you can cancel the whole invoice with our module and place a new order afterwards.  Easily generate credit notes of the full invoice This module allows you to generate full credit notes for any invoices that have been issued and then cancelled. The module is very easy to use: select the order number you want to cancel and click on the button "Create". Then click on the PDF icon to download/open it.  PDF credit notes The module creates credit notes in PDF format that you can easily send to your clients. Each credit notes contains:the store logothe billing and delivery addressthe credit note details (issued date and number)the order details (date, number, payment method and carrier)the ordered products (name, attributes, reference, unit price tax excl., unit price incl., discount, quantity and total tax incl.)the total calculation (product total tax excl., product total tax incl., shipping cost, total tax and total)]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[99.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[59.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/671608-pprod/credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/671608-pbig/credit-notes-memos-of-the-complete-invoice-in-pdf.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7152]]></id><name><![CDATA[customfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Fields]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Gestione del contenuto]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/content-management/7152-custom-fields.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7152.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create unlimited number of custom fields for registration form. You can add all kinds of fields: text, text area, radio buttons, check boxes and select lists with unlimited number of options and more.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[It's important to know about as much as possible about customers. It will help with better understanding of the clients habits and needs. That knowledge will allow e-merchant to improve it's services and finally make more profit of his business. Custom fields module in easy way allows you to create unlimited number of custom fields and get all required data about your customers that cannot be done with standard registration form. All fields can be validated with selected validation rule and can be viewed and editable in the backoffice.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[54.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pprod/custom-fields.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/582276-pbig/custom-fields.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price increment/discount by customer groups]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/7422-price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module lets you&nbsp;apply an increment or a discount to product price depending on the customer&#39;s group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Apply different price to&nbsp;the product&nbsp;depending on the group that customer belongs toApply a markup to your products]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/569002-pprod/price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/569002-pbig/price-increment-discount-by-customer-groups.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8066]]></id><name><![CDATA[paybox]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Paybox (1.5 & 1.6)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pagamento]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumenta le tue vendite proponendo il pagamento con carta bancaria in tutta sicurezza grazie al modulo Paybox!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/pagamento-prestashop-moduli/8066-paybox.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8066.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumenta le tue vendite proponendo il pagamento con carta bancaria in tutta sicurezza grazie al modulo Paybox!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Dedicato ai commercianti che si trovano in tutta Europa, Paybox elabora attualmente i flussi di più di 37,000 commercianti e 120 milioni di transazioni all'anno. Questa soluzione di pagamento con carta bancaria ti permette di offrire numerosi servizi come per esempio:il pagamento a ratela possibilità di scegliere tra un addebito differito, immediato o alla spedizioneuna sicurezza adatta alle esigenze del tuo negozio con il 3D Secure selettivo a seconda dell'importo del carrello del clienteuna soluzione multilingue e multivaluta per aprirti a livello internazionalele funzionalità avanzate del pacchetto Flessibile (Paybox System + Direct)una funzione di rimborso parziale o totale di un ordine a partire dal Back-Office PrestaShop]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[279.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[184.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611629-pprod/paybox.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/611629-pbig/paybox.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8244]]></id><name><![CDATA[ec_seo404]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO - disabled and deleted 301 redirect Products]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Indicizzazione – SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product]]></description><author><![CDATA[Ether Création]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/seo-moduli-prestashop/8244-seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8244.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[End with 404 pages and referencing loss for disabled or deleted product. You will be able to choose for each case a 301, 302 redirection, home page or default category (Ideal for SEO)]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Whenever a product will be deactivated or deleted, you will be able to assign a redirect (permanent: 301 not found: 404 temporary: 302, an url internal or external to your web site, the home page of your site or default category).  No need to turn your catalog to know what your pages are no longer valid link, the module will tell you. And this whatever the language or the store (if multi-boutique). In addition, you can manually add a link of your choice. You can edit multiple products at the same time to save time if the rule is the same (parent category, home, etc ...)  You can define rules that will, in the future, when a product is disabled / deleted, created a redirection to a desired page.  When a product is reactivated, forwarding rules automatically deactivate.  Not overload your HTACCESS file and therefore no notion necessary to make it work, or any slowdown in browsing your site.  All referrals are importable one by one or en masse from a csv file whose example is provided.  So your referenced links will be redirected with confidence to not lose your positioning.  Through a system of colors, get a look to the status of your referrals to know what will or not : - White => redirection is active! - Green => as possible redirection for disabled or deleted page but the redirection is not active. - Orange => can Redirection for disabled or deleted page but the redirection is not active and no link is entered for the redirection. - Grey => redirection is inactive because the page has been reactivated. - Red => Redirection enabled, but not here! So page 404 usual!  You also get a filter system depending on the state (broken links, error redirection, redirection to, etc ...) in order to act accordingly quickly.  With this module no more broken links on your site!  Two other augmented versions of the modules exist : -  one with category page more : http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/11258-seo-404-301-product-and-category-delete-or-disable.html  - The other pages with categories, brands, founisseurs, cms and specific urls! http://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-prestashop-modules/18272-301-seo-automatic-redirection-of-all-your-404.html  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/683583-pprod/seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/683583-pbig/seo-disabled-and-deleted-301-redirect-products.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8458]]></id><name><![CDATA[wic_pushproductcms]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push Products on CMS Pages]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandizing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages]]></description><author><![CDATA[Web In Color]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/merchandizing-prestashop-modulo/8458-push-products-on-cms-pages.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8458.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to display a block with the products you want on your CMS pages. Use all the pages of your website and increase your sales!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module oriented Merchandising allows you to optimize all your pages, including these you thought it was not possible (Shipping, Secure Payment, Legals, etc..)Highlight a selection of products on your CMS pages.Configure these products by CMS pages directly from your back office easely.Increase your sales.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[64.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/582794-pprod/push-products-on-cms-pages.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/582794-pbig/push-products-on-cms-pages.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Legge Europea sui Cookies (Avviso + Blocker del Cookie)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Il solo modulo che ti permette di conformarti alla normativa europea e alla legge italiana sui cookie nota come “cookie law”]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/8734-legge-europea-sui-cookies-avviso-blocker-del-cookie.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Il solo modulo che ti permette di conformarti alla normativa europea e alla legge italiana sui cookie nota come “cookie law”. Visualizza un banner di notifica e disattiva i cookie all'accesso dei visitatori fino a che non ottieni il loro consenso.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Il nostro modulo è completamente conforme alla normativa europea e alla cookie law.  Conformità completa alla Cookie Law  Oltre a visualizzare un banner di notifica, questo è l'unico modulo che ti permette di bloccare i cookie all'accesso dei visitatori al tuo negozio.  Contrariamente ad altri moduli che fanno apparire solo un banner di notifica senza richiedere il consenso, lasciando i cookie installarsi sul computer dell'utente a sua insaputa, il nostro modulo è l'unico in grado di bloccare i cookie prima della richiesta del consenso.  Funzioni principali del moduloVisualizzazione di un banner di notifica per informare gli utenti sull'uso dei cookie e per richiedere il loro consensoDisattivazione dei moduli che utilizzano i cookie all'accesso degli utenti sul sito  poiché : "Quando gli utenti visitano un sito o utilizzano un'applicazione, essi devono essere informati e dare il proprio consenso prima dell'inserimento o della lettura dei cookie o di altri file traccianti" .Attivazione dei cookie dopo l'ottenimento del consenso o in caso di mantenimento della disattivazione, se l'utente rifiuta l'utilizzo di cookieCompleta personalizzazione del banner di notifica (colore, testo, link, font, posizione, modalità multilingue, trasparenza...)   Ottenimento del consenso   Il modulo include 2 modalità differenti di accettazione dei cookie, puoi scegliere tra:Accettazione mediante pulsante: l'utente deve cliccare sul pulsante "Accetto i cookie" nel banner di notifica per dare il proprio consenso. A partire dal momento in cui l'utente dà il proprio consenso, il banner di notifica sparisce e tutti i moduli che utilizzano i cookie si attiveranno e funzioneranno normalmente. Se invece l'utente non accetta i cookie i moduli disattivati resteranno inattivi. Ti consigliamo di utilizzare questa modalità per conformarti completamente alle direttive europee sull'uso dei cookie.Accettazione mediante navigazione con scomparsa del banner: il fatto di proseguire la navigazione sul sito viene considerato come un'accettazione dei cookie. Il banner di notifica appare sulla prima pagina sulla quale l'utente accede con un messaggio del tipo "Proseguendo la navigazione del sito si acconsente all'uso dei cookie". Quando l'utente decide di continuare a navigare sul sito e visita un'altra pagina del sito, il banner scompare e i moduli disattivati vengono attivati. Contenuto e personalizzazione del banner  Come raccomandato dalla cookie law, il modulo permette di personalizzare il messaggio che appare nel banner di notifica (al fine di informare sui cookie usati e sulla loro finalità) e di aggiungere nel banner un pulsante "Maggiori informazioni", che rimanda a una pagina CMS del tuo sito (per spiegare nei dettagli l'utilizzo dei cookie sul tuo sito)  Il banner di notifica è di tipo responsive e si adatta alla larghezza della finestra. Il modulo integra un editor Wysiwyg che permette di personalizzare completamente il contenuto del banner (font, colore, effetti, codice html...). Puoi anche scegliere dalla pagina di configurazione il colore dello sfondo del banner, la percentuale di opacità (trasparenza) e la sua posizione (in alto o in basso dello schermo). Inoltre il modulo è multilingue e rileva automaticamente tutte le lingue del tuo negozio, permettendoti di configurare un messaggio diverso a seconda della lingua.  Nota: il modulo è progettato per non visualizzare il banner di notifica quando i crawler dei motori di ricerca visitano il tuo sito al fine di non comprometterne la visibilità.  Disattivazione dei moduli  È l'unico modulo che ti permette di disattivare momentaneamente i moduli che utilizzano i cookie fino a che l'utente dà il proprio consenso. Questa funzione è essenziale poiché "Quando gli utenti visitano un sito o usano un'applicazione, questi devono essere informati e dare il proprio consenso prima dell'inserimento o della lettura dei cookie o di altri file traccianti"  Modalità multinegozio  Il modulo è compatibile con la modalità multinegozio e permette di visualizzare lo stesso banner di notifica su ognuno dei tuoi negozi, ma il consenso è comune a tutte le boutique. Se accetti l'uso dei cookie su uno dei tuoi negozi, il modulo considererà come accettati i cookie di tutti i tuoi negozi (da precisare nella tua Privacy policy) e il banner di notifica non verrà visualizzato quando visiterai gli altri tuoi negozi.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[24.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/671485-pprod/legge-europea-sui-cookies-avviso-blocker-del-cookie.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/671485-pbig/legge-europea-sui-cookies-avviso-blocker-del-cookie.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Push on Cart]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prezzi & Promozioni]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumenta facilmente il valore medio del carrello offrendo sconti personalizzati ai tuoi clienti nel riepilogo del carrello degli acquisti]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/prezzi-promozioni-prestashop-moduli/11345-push-on-cart.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumenta facilmente il valore medio del carrello offrendo sconti personalizzati ai tuoi clienti nel riepilogo del carrello degli acquisti.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Con il modulo Push on Cart puoi: Aumentare facilmente il valore medio del carrello dei tuoi clienti Smaltire i prodotti invenduti di tua scelta Aiutare i clienti a scoprire nuovi prodotti e a creare domanda Migliorare la soddisfazione e la fedeltà dei clienti grazie a sconti personalizzati su prodotti selezionati]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/push-on-cart.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/push-on-cart.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Point of Sale (POS) pro by PrestaMonster]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Merchandizing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Grazie a Point of Sale pro, ora puoi vendere i tuoi prodotti sia online che offline nei tuoi negozi / magazzini / mostre, fiere campionarie o via telefono / chat]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaMonster]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/merchandizing-prestashop-modulo/13654-point-of-sale-pos-pro-by-prestamonster.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Grazie a Point of Sale pro, ora puoi vendere i tuoi prodotti sia online che offline nei tuoi negozi / magazzini / mostre, fiere campionarie o via telefono / chat. Tutte le transazioni sono collegate al tuo database cloud.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ Vendi i tuoi prodotti ovunque e da qualsiasi luogo in pochi secondi.Accentra i dati, senza bisogno di tempo in più per raccogliere i tuoi ordini manuali.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/618511-pprod/point-of-sale-pos-pro-by-prestamonster.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/618511-pbig/point-of-sale-pos-pro-by-prestamonster.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[cartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sollecito di carrelli abbandonati]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Processo d’ordine]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Migliora il tasso di trasformazione di più del 15% grazie alle e-mail di sollecito di carrelli abbandonati, e proponi anche degli sconti per invogliare di più a convertire!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/moduli-prestashop-processo-ordine-checkout/16535-abandoned-cart-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Migliora il tasso di trasformazione di più del 15% grazie alle e-mail di sollecito di carrelli abbandonati, e proponi anche degli sconti per invogliare di più a convertire!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatizza in pochi clic l'invio di un'e-mail di sollecito in seguito a un carrello abbandonato.Aggiungi facilmente uno sconto (o delle spese di spedizione gratuite) sul messaggio secondo l'importo del carrello per ottimizzare le tue conversioni.Massimizza le tue trasformazioni inviando 1, 2 o 3 solleciti quando vuoi, e nelle lingue che desideri. Approfitta di uno strumento intuitivo, configurabile molto facilmente e completamente personalizzabile con i colori del tuo negozio. Non perdere più i tuoi clienti esitanti! Crea molto rapidamente delle e-mail automatiche per sollecitare i carrelli che non si sono conclusi con un pagamento. Commenti: Postato il 30-08-2014 - ID ordine: ﻿#232568 «Il modulo migliore che ho acquistato su prestashop, semplice da installare e da utilizzare, il top del top!»]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.5.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pprod/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595057-pbig/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO EXPERT Indicizzazione]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Indicizzazione – SEO]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumenta il traffico entrando nella prima pagina dei risultati di ricerca]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/seo-moduli-prestashop/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumenta il traffico entrando nella prima pagina dei risultati di ricerca.  Il modulo Esperto SEO compila automaticamente i meta tag e i meta tag per social media per ottimizzare il tuo negozio online e garantire una maggiore visibilità nei motori di ricerca e sulle piattaforme di social media.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Crea automaticamente meta tag per risparmiare oltre 40 ore.  Con il modulo Esperto SEO:        Il tuo sito verrà visualizzato sulla prima pagina dei risultati nei motori di ricerca quali Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, ecc.Incrementa le vendite con un maggiore traffico Web Migliora la visibilità del tuo negozio per ogni linguaAumenta le conversioni con traffico qualificatoMetti in risalto il tuo negozio con regole interamente personalizzate per le pagine relative a prodotti e categorieSfrutta Facebook e Twitter per acquisire un numero crescente di clientiOttimizza il tuo negozio online per i social media con titoli condivisi adattatiCogli l'occasione per acquistare il modulo al prezzo di lancio!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[219.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17261]]></id><name><![CDATA[shipcloud]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[shipcloud - Shipping Tool for DHL, Hermes, UPS etc]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Trasporto & Logistica]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Shipcloud is a simple and unique way to manage all your shipping options within only one PrestaShop Module. Currently, services from DHL, Hermes, UPS, DPD, GLS and IOXX are supported]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/trasporto-logistica-moduli-prestashop/17261-shipcloud-shipping-tool-for-dhl-hermes-ups-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17261.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Shipcloud is a simple and unique way to manage all your shipping options within only one PrestaShop Module. Currently, services from DHL, Hermes, UPS, DPD, GLS and IOXX are supported. &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Offer your merchants multiple shipping options with only one shipcloud accountNew in 2.0Mass processing Now You can generate several labels in one move and save them in PDF file. Also existing labels can be printed out again.Several Labels for one oder  Unlimited number of labels for each oderCreate return labels  Now return labels can be generated directly from the Back OfficeNew shipping servicesFedexLiferyUpdate shipping services directly from your Back Office All shipping services plugged subsequently can be updated from the Back OfficeOrder Reference or Order ID  optionally, the &bdquo;Oder Reference&ldquo; or &bdquo;Oder ID&ldquo; can be selected to display on the labelExtra Insurance for DHL and Fedex directly from the Back OfficeDifferent shipping options for DHL  For DHL different shipping options can be selectedStandartExpressExpress till 10 o&rsquo;clock BenefitsCreate shipping labels for the following shipping servicesDHL,DPD,UPS,Hermes,GLSILOXXYou can handle everything with only onbe Shipcloud AccountDirect label printing from the PrestaShop BackendAutomatic tracking code creation in the order detailsYou can define a global weights / sizes for every shipping service with the availability to modify this data on the shipping labelTracking goes directly from order details screenDisplay porto/shipping on the shipping labelsMultishop supportFeaturesNo shipping data exportNo manually creating of shipping labels anymore. Just print them out with your PrestaShop BackOffice, labels will be generated in real time and are pre-configured for the apropriate shipping serviceno extra agreement with the shipping provider needed, it is organized centrally by shipcloud. But you can you your existing agreement data to get connected with your serviceShipcloud supports the shipping methods within the EUshipcloud enables the worldwide shipping with FedEX and UPS.  shipcloud enables shipping for DPD from AT, CH and Benelux countries. Other Carriers are available for shipping only from Germany.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650103-pprod/shipcloud-shipping-tool-for-dhl-hermes-ups-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650103-pbig/shipcloud-shipping-tool-for-dhl-hermes-ups-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17452]]></id><name><![CDATA[giftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Buono Sconto]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prezzi & Promozioni]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumenta le tue vendite e ottieni più clienti proponendo loro la possibilità di offrire il regalo perfetto senza correre rischi grazie al modulo Buono Sconto sviluppato da PrestaShop! Pratiche e sempli]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/prezzi-promozioni-prestashop-moduli/17452-buono-sconto.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17452.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumenta le tue vendite e ottieni più clienti proponendo loro la possibilità di offrire il regalo perfetto senza correre rischi grazie al modulo Buono Sconto sviluppato da PrestaShop! Pratiche e semplici, le carte regalo si posizionano in cima alla classifica dei regali più gettonati!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Questa soluzione permette di offrire carte regalo di qualsiasi valore nel tuo negozio.  Ogni cliente può acquistare una carta regalo per dare la possibilità ad altri di visitare il tuo negozio e farvi acquisti.    Questo modulo ti permette di: Trovare nuovi clienti: i destinatari delle carte regalo rappresentano un mercato di nuovi potenziali clienti! Aumentare le tue vendite: i destinatari delle carte regalo spesso spendono più dell'importo pagato per la carta stessa. Incoraggiare clienti indecisi ad acquistare: se offri un semplice regalo, adatto a tutti i tipi di cliente, essi non esiteranno più.   Il mercato delle carte regalo dimostra un grande successo con i consumatori e la sua crescita annuale oscilla fra il 20 e il 40%.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[124.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/597595-pprod/buono-sconto.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/597595-pbig/buono-sconto.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17522]]></id><name><![CDATA[lengow]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[LENGOW]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Marketplaces e reselling]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Google Shopping, Amazon, Trovaprezzi, Criteo, Ebay… utilizzando Lengow diffondete i vostri prodotti esattamente dove si trovano i vostri clienti (+di 1200 flussi suportati in  Francia, UK, Germania, S]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/marketplace-affiliation-prestashop-moduli/17522-lengow-new.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17522.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Google Shopping, Amazon, Trovaprezzi, Criteo, Ebay… utilizzando Lengow diffondete i vostri prodotti esattamente dove si trovano i vostri clienti (+di 1200 flussi suportati in  Francia, UK, Germania, Spagna, Brasile…).]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Centralizzate la gestione dei vostri prodotti sulle marketplaces, comparatori di prezzo… In Francia e all'estero grazie ad una sola piattaforma. Beneficiate di un cruscotto di gestione che vi permette d'ottimizzare le vostre performance. Gestite facilmente gli ordini generati sulle marketplaces. Avvantaggiatevi dell'esperienza di Lengow, leader europeo nella gestione di flussi prodotto (product feed).]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.10]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/598951-pprod/lengow-new.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/598951-pbig/lengow-new.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17545]]></id><name><![CDATA[veplatform]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[VePlatform: Conversioni da carrelli abbandonati ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pubblicità & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Aumenta immediatamente le tue vendite! Converti i consumatori che abbandonano il tuo sito aggiungendo le apps di remarketing e re-engagement di VePlatform  Clicca qui e connettiti a VePlatform adesso!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/pubblicita-marketing-newsletter-moduli/17545-veplatform-conversioni-da-carrelli-abbandonati.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/17545.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Aumenta immediatamente le tue vendite! Converti i consumatori che abbandonano il tuo sito aggiungendo le apps di remarketing e re-engagement di VePlatform  Clicca qui e connettiti a VePlatform adesso!  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Integrando VePlatform avrai un accesso immediato alle suite delle conversioni potenziando le apps di remarketing e re-engagement create per:Ridurre il tuo bounce rateAumentare l’interazione con il consumatoreAumentare le conversioni riducendo gli abbandoniGenerare un ROI più alto dalle tue campagneGarantire l’incremento dei ricavi]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[15.2.300]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[18967]]></id><name><![CDATA[livechatpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Live Chat Pro (Responsive)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Funzionalità Front Office]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to chat with your visitors, track their behavior on your site in real time and view their geolocation using google maps. Many operators can chat with several users at once]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/funzionalita-front-office-moduli-prestashop/18967-live-chat-pro-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/18967.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to chat with your visitors, track their behavior on your site in real time and view their geolocation using google maps. Many operators can chat with several users at once.  &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[A study called &ldquo;Making Proactive Chat Work&rdquo; &nbsp;found the following:&nbsp; Many online consumers want help from a live person while they are shopping online; in fact, 44% of online consumers say that having questions answered by a live person while in the middle of an online purchase is one of the most important features a Web site can offer.  An ATG Global Consumer Trend study found that 90% of customers consider live chat helpful 62% reported being more likely to purchase from the site again. A further 38% of respondents said they had made their purchase due to the chat session itself. All these attitudes were even more prevalent among respondents who bought online at least weekly. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.7.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Partner Agency"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-partner-agency.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/663545-pprod/live-chat-pro-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/663545-pbig/live-chat-pro-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19198]]></id><name><![CDATA[couponpop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Coupon Pop: Convert Visitors to Paying Customers]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pubblicità & Marketing]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase Your Leads &amp; Sales Today by Offering Your Visitors a Coupon Code in Return for Following You on Social Network or for Subscribing to Your Newsletter]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/pubblicita-marketing-newsletter-moduli/19198-coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19198.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase Your Leads &amp; Sales Today by Offering Your Visitors a Coupon Code in Return for Following You on Social Network or for Subscribing to Your Newsletter. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[33% Average Increase in Monthly Sales25% Average Increase in Fans &amp; Followers Growth2 min Install+100,000 Happy Merchants]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/653241-pprod/coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/653241-pbig/coupon-pop-convert-visitors-to-paying-customers.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19245]]></id><name><![CDATA[emtshipping]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[QuickDelivery - Spedizioni a misura di e-commerce!]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Trasporto & Logistica]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Spedite in Italia e nel mondo direttamente dal vostro back-office : semplice, conveniente, integrato – Zero costi di attivazione    ]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/trasporto-logistica-moduli-prestashop/19245-quickdelivery-spedizioni-a-misura-di-e-commerce.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19245.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Spedite in Italia e nel mondo direttamente dal vostro back-office : semplice, conveniente, integrato – Zero costi di attivazione    ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Con il modulo QuickDelivery di e-motion|made4ecommerce potete spedire in Italia e nel mondo direttamente dal vostro back-office con tariffe chiare, senza nessun costo aggiuntivo e pagando esclusivamente a consumo! Dopo l’installazione, basterà un semplice click per avere accesso ai nostri servizi QuickDelivery Italia e QuickDelivery Export che vi consentiranno di spedire ovunque conoscendo in anticipo i costi, senza impegni di volume o di fatturato e con un’unica interfaccia per tutte le vostre spedizioni!   ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.28]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.0.14]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[19395]]></id><name><![CDATA[cart2cart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: Modulo di Migrazione PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Strumenti di Importo / CMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: Modulo di Migrazione PrestaShop permette l’elaborazione automatizzata da 60+ piattaforme e-Commerce a PrestaShop o PrestaShop Cloud senza che siano richieste alcune capacità  programming sk]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/cms-prestashop-moduli/19395-cart2cart-modulo-di-migrazione-prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19395.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Cart2Cart: Modulo di Migrazione PrestaShop permette l’elaborazione automatizzata da 60+ piattaforme e-Commerce a PrestaShop o PrestaShop Cloud senza che siano richieste alcune capacità  programming skills required.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Migrazione Demo gratuita – provate come funziona la migrazione spostando un numero limitato di entità da PrestaShop in 10-30 min.100% uptime  - il processo di migrazione non ha effetto sulle prestazioni del vostro attuale negozio.Prezzo flessibile – il costo della migrazione dipende interamente dalla somma delle entità da trasferire.Non sono necessarie capacità di programmazione – Il processo di migrazione è interamente automatizzato e richiede minima interferenza da parte dell’utente.Assistenza diligente -Un team di assistenza professionale è pronto ad offire il suo aiuto e a rispondere a qualsiasi domanda riferita al processo di migrazione attraverso segnalazione, telefono o chat.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[migration_tools]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price></module><module><id><![CDATA[19927]]></id><name><![CDATA[quotation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Devis en ligne]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Prezzi & Promozioni]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for an estimate in your online shop! With the &ldquo;Online quotation&rdquo; module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products the]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[http://addons.prestashop.com/it/prezzi-promozioni-prestashop-moduli/19927-online-quotation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-IT&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/img/pico/19927.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allow customers to ask for an estimate in your online shop! With the &ldquo;Online quotation&rdquo; module, create a made-to-measure form so your customers can ask for an estimate for the products they are interested in and you pick up all the information you needed to create an estimate.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase the conversion rate of your shop by making an attractive offer by estimateIncrease the average shopping cart by encouraging your customers to buy more products they hadn&rsquo;t planned toAllow your customers to order personalised items using offers by estimateOptimise your shop&rsquo;s reassurance and customer satisfaction by advising your customers using estimates&nbsp; Make a personalised study and follow-up of every estimate request you receive. Send your proposal to your customer, who can turn the estimate into an order with a single click. &nbsp; Our tip: A few days after sending the estimate, send a reminder e-mail using the &ldquo;Abandoned Cart Reminder Pro&rdquo; module&nbsp; &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[174.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://addons-media.prestashop.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/676340-pprod/online-quotation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/676340-pbig/online-quotation.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>